It's probably that kid.
多分、あの子だね
Oh, maybe?
ああ、多分ですか
Oh, it's that kid.
ああ、あの子だね
It's my first time though.
初めてだけど
No, it's a cat encounter.
いや、猫の出会いだよ
Yuki-chan, it's been a while.
ゆきちゃん、久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
I missed you.
会いたかったよ
会いたかったです
picture?
え?
dazzling?
眩しい?
dazzling.
眩しい
picture?
え?
It's been a long time.
めっちゃ久々だね
It's been a while.
久々です
hey.
ね
The atmosphere hasn't changed.
雰囲気変わってないね
It hasn't changed.
変わってないです
hey.
ね
They also wore their uniforms properly.
ちゃんと制服も着てくれたんだね
I've worn it.
着てきました
picture?
え?
What are you reading?
何読んでるの?
What were you reading?
何読んでたの?
I was reading girls' manga.
少女漫画読んでた
Have you read girls' manga?
少女漫画読んでたの?
Too cute.
可愛すぎる
copper?
どう?
Since then.
あれから
Since then, I've been using it properly in elementary school.
あれから、ちゃんと小学期に当てました
Really?
本当に?
It's true.
本当ですよ
Oh, that's great.
おお、えらい
That's great.
えらいね
hey.
ね
Eh, is it okay to be seen?
えー、見ばれとかは大丈夫?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Right now.
今 んとこ
The uniform suits you.
制服似合ってんじゃん
Just try it on.
ちょっと着てみて
Isn't it nice?
いいじゃないですか
thank you.
ありがとうございます
You can sit down for a while.
ちょっと座っていいよ
Okay, so let's check this.
はい、じゃあこれのチェックということで
Well, here we are.
あれ、こっちはついた
This one is here.
こっちはついた
Still, then is that it?
まだ、じゃああれですか
Um, with my boyfriend.
あの、彼氏と
That's because it's still going on.
まだ続いてるということで
It's piping hot.
熱々です
Is it piping hot?
熱々ですか
I see.
なるほどね
It's piping hot.
熱々です
Last time, um, what do you say?
前回はさ、あの、何て言うの
Well, there was an actor, a slightly different actor.
まあ、男優さんさ、ちょっと違った男優さんいたじゃん
yes.
はい
So, the number of people with experience, um, was said to be able to fit in one hand.
で、経験人数だったりさ、あの、片手で収まるって言われだった
However, today I brought a different actor with me.
けど、 ちょっと今日は違う男優さんちょっと連れてきたから、
Aim for both hands.
両手を目指してね
両手を目指して
That's right, I aim to have both hands.
そうそうそう、両手になるようにっていうのを目指して、
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I will do my best.
頑張ります
Um, well, I think it's something like that, I wish I could do it.
あのー、まあそんな感じでね、やっていければなと思うけどさ
copper?
どう?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張しちゃう
Are you still nervous?
まだ緊張してる?
No, but it's not my first time.
いや、 だけどさ、はじめましてじゃないじゃん
It's not my first time.
はじめましてじゃないけど
Well, last time it was at night.
で、前回はさ、夜だったじゃん
That's right, that's why, this time...
そうそうそう、だからさ、今回はさ、
Yeah, yeah, just a little bit.
そうそう そうそう、ちょっとさ、
What do you say?
なんて言うの
The weather is so nice, I'm so lucky
こんな天気いいしさ、せっかくさ、
Hey, this park, that's what it is,
ちょっとさ、この公園さ、あれだからさ、
How about a little walk?
ちょっと散歩でも、どうですか?
good?
いい?
Let's go.
行きましょう
good?
いい?
Well then, before we take a little walk,
じゃ、ちょっと散歩の前にじゃあ、
a little bit.
ちょっと
picture?
え?
yes.
はい
A glimpse.
チラッと
See you then.
じゃあなー
Is it true?
はずい?
Oh, lol.
あら、おろろろろ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Oh, is that the end?
あ、おしまいですか?
It's over.
おしまい
Is your service time over?
サービスタイムおしまいですか?
That's it.
おしまいです
It's only for a moment.
一瞬だけです
Just for a moment?
一瞬だけ?
Well, there are a lot of people.
まあ、いっぱい人いるからね
Well then, let's take a little walk.
じゃあ、じゃあちょっと散歩していこうか
yes.
はい
good?
いい?
Yuki-chan, aren't you feeling good?
ゆきちゃん気持ちくない?
It's warm.
温かいですね
Hey, it's warm.
ね、温かいよね
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
It's not cold.
寒くないです
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Just about right.
ちょ う ど いいくらい
Really?
本当に?
Yuki-chan, there you go, the video.
ゆきちゃんさ、 あのさ、動画さ、
Wow, it was well received.
すごい、なんか、好評だったよ
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうですか?
Yeah.
うん
happy?
嬉しい?
I'm happy.
嬉しいですよ
Aren't you happy?
嬉 しく はない?
happy?
嬉しい?
You're a happy person, really.
嬉しい方ですよ、本当に
Oh, really?
あ、本当に?
Good.
よかったわ
Well, that's it, try some things.
まあ、それでさ、いろいろやってみてくれ、
There was a voice saying, ``Try this!''
これやってみてくれ、とかっていう声がさ、
Because there were a lot.
多かったからさ
There is such a thing.
そんなのあるんだ
yes.
そう
Just wondering how far I can go today.
ちょっと今日どこまでできるんだろうっていうのをさ、
I see.
なるほど
Yes, I was thinking of trying it out.
そう、ちょっと試したいなと思ってんだけどさ
Yuki-chan, what do you want to do?
ゆきちゃん、何したい?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Sex during this time.
この間のセックス
Yeah.
うん
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Normally.
普通に
Really?
本当に?
Today, as I said earlier,
今日はさ、さっきも言ったけどさ、
Hey, my feet aren't quite right.
ちょっとあの、ちょっと足元悪いね
Shall we go this way?
こっち行こうか
As I said earlier, what are you talking about today?
今日はさ、なんていうの、さっきも言ったけどさ、
He brought in a different actor.
男優さん、違う男優さん連れてきたとかさ、
I was wondering if I would mess with her a lot.
いっぱいイジクリ倒しちゃうかなと思ってんだけど
I see.
なるほど
copper?
どう?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
good?
いい?
I thought I'd just mess around with it.
イジクリ倒しまくっちゃおうかなと思って
That's it.
そんな
Yeah.
うん
I was wondering if I should mess around with it that much.
そんだけイジクっちゃおうかなと思ってんだけど
I see, I see.
なるほど、なるほど
copper?
どう?
good?
いい?
Cute, cute.
かわいい、かわいい
As always, it's cute.
相変わらず、かわいいね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
But don't you have a boyfriend?
だけど、彼氏いるんじゃない?
But my boyfriend.
だけど、彼氏は
My boyfriend is cute.
かわいいんで、彼氏は
What is it like to have a boyfriend?
彼氏とはさ、どんな感じなの?
now.
今
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
I've asked this question before, but I'm going to ask the same question again.
この、前もさ聞いたけどさ、また同じ質問になっちゃうけどさ、
Well, what do you say?
まあ、なんていうの
It's hot again, isn't there a mark?
また熱いさ、マークあるじゃないですか
yes.
はい
hey.
ね
So, I don't know what to say.
だからさ、ちょっと、なんて言うんだろうな
It's okay, don't appeal like that.
いいですよ、そんなアピールしなくて
Well, I wonder what you'll say.
まあ、なんて言うんだろうな
It looks a bit like Matara, but I think it's a bit of a bruise.
ちょっと、まーたらしい、ちょっとアザなのかなと思ってるけど
difference.
さ
It seems like a real thing.
ま ーたらしい
What happened at the end?
その最後、どうなった?
When is it?
いつですか?
picture?
え?
At the end, I spent a passionate night with my boyfriend.
その最後、彼氏と熱い夜を過ごしたのは
It was yesterday.
昨日です
Was it yesterday?
昨日ですか
I see.
そっか
We had a hot night yesterday.
昨日じゃ熱い夜を過ごして
I spent it.
過ごしました
Maybe just to rub off on that hot night.
その熱い夜をこすぐらい、多分
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
Yeah.
うん
Today too.
今日も
It's going to become.
なっていくよ
I'm really thinking about messing with it.
もう本当にいじり倒しちゃおうかなと思ってるからさ
Wow, great momentum.
おー、すごい勢い
By the way, isn't the need for that kind of experience increasing?
あれさ、ちなみにさ、その経験ニーズ増えてない?
Since then.
あれから
It's from then, isn't it?
あれからですよね
It won't increase in one month.
1ヶ月で増えないですよ
yes?
そう?
It doesn't increase in about 2 months after 1 month.
1ヶ月で2ヶ月くらいで増えないです
Doesn't it increase?
増えない?
It cannot increase.
増えないです
Then it seems okay.
じゃあ大丈夫そうだね
Well, today is the day.
じゃあ今日で、行程になるね
It's finally time to go.
やっと行程になるね
During this time, if I remember correctly,
この間で、おじさんの記憶が正しければさ、
They said there were four of them the other day, but recently he became the fifth actor.
この間4人って言ってて、この間の男優さんで5人目ってなって、
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
I was told that today was the journey,
今日はだから行程だよって言われて、
That was it,
あれだったんだけど、
That's why I hope to gradually heal myself.
だから 徐々に徐々に癒していければなと思っててね
gradually?
徐 々に?
Little by little.
少しずつ
少しずつね
Yuki-chan, do you like sex?
ゆきちゃん、セックスは好きなの?
picture?
え?
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
But I think it's better not to hate it.
でも嫌いではない方がいいかなって
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
I see.
そっか
Well, I hope we can do a lot of things today as well.
じゃあ今日もね、いろいろとしていけたらなと思うからさ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Okay, I thought it would be this early.
いいよ、こんな早くあれかなって
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
It's cute, it's sex.
かわいいね、セックスね
No way.
うそー
Yeah.
うん
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
やだ、恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
why?
なんで?
You're not that old to be embarrassed about.
恥ずかしい歳じゃないじゃんだって
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですよ
After all, I just graduated the other day.
だってこないだ卒業したばっかりですよね
I just did it, but it's embarrassing.
したばっかですけど、恥ずかしい
why?
なんで?
Are you embarrassed already?
もう恥ずかしいの?
what?
何?
Maybe you feel like an old lady already?
もしかしてもうおばさんになった気分なの?
Yeah.
うん
Really?
本当に?
Everyone will get mad at that.
みんなに怒られちゃうよ、それ
Isn't it cold in the shade?
日陰寒くない?
It's a little cold.
ちょっと冷える
Let's go this way.
こっち行こうよ
It's cold in the shade.
日陰寒いわ
It's cold, cold.
寒い寒い
There's a wind.
風がする
Like this, there are a lot of people.
こういうさ、いっぱい人いるじゃん、
At the park.
公園で
Everyone does things like exercise and sports.
運動とかさ、スポーツとかみんなしてんじゃん
What do you think?
どうなの?
Yuki-chan, what about sports?
ゆきちゃん、スポーツは?
Not at all.
全然しないですよ
lie?
嘘?
What about club activities?
部活動は?
I didn't go to middle school though.
中学はしてなかったけど
what have you been up to?
何してたの?
Soft tennis.
ソフトテニス
Is it soft tennis?
ソフトテニスか
I want to play soft tennis.
ソフトテニスしたい
ソフトテニスやりたいね
not at all.
全然
Completely?
全 然?
Why?
下 手 なんで
It's not that I'm bad at it, I just want to do it.
下手とかじゃないってさ、やりたいじゃん
But I haven't seen the break.
でも休憩見てないんですよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Playing during breaks is no good.
休憩遊びはダメなんだ
No play during breaks.
休憩遊びダメ
Instead of playing during the break, why not try 50m soft?
休憩遊びじゃなくて、50メートルソフトやってみる?
30m soft?
30メートルソフトか
No, I'll die.
いや、死ぬ
Because, look.
だって、見て
picture?
え?
Looks like it's going to be easy to run today.
今日なって、走りやすそうな
I'm not running.
走ってない
Haven't you been running lately?
最近走ってない?
I'm not running.
走ってないです
It's not running.
走ってないね
I'm not running.
走ってないです
I see.
そっか
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
It's cold.
寒いね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Well then, use it for hot drinks or something.
じゃあ、暖かい飲み物とかでも使ってさ、
I want to go back to the car and go to the hotel right away.
車戻ってさ、車行って、早速ホテルに行きたいなと思うんだけど
difference.
さ
I see.
なるほど
good?
いい?
good.
いい
Well then, let's go to a hotel.
じゃあ、 そしたらじゃあ、ホテル行こうかな
good?
いい?
snow
ゆ き
Sorry, I said I was going to a hotel.
ちゃん、 ごめんね、ホテル行くって言ったけどさ、
Before that, I feel like having a light meal.
ちょっとその前に、そう、ちょっと軽くご飯食べたくなっちゃ
It was.
った
copper?
どう?
What do you think of this place that I just stopped by?
軽 く寄ったところが、こういうところはどうですか?
I was surprised at how fashionable it was.
おしゃれですごいびっくりしました
It's fashionable, isn't it?
おしゃれでしょ
I was surprised.
びっくりしました
This kind of thing is, after all, what is it?
こういうのはさ、やっぱりあの、なに、
Your boyfriend won't take you with him, right?
彼氏にはさ、連れてってもらえないでしょ、
This kind of place.
こういうところは
That's right, it's fashionable.
そうだよね、おしゃれだよね
It's fashionable.
おしゃれですね
You can eat it, absolutely.
食べていいよ、全然
What is that?
なに、あれ?
After all, teenagers like to drink orange juice during meals.
なんかやっぱり、10代はさ、食事中にはオレンジジュースとか
Well, I don't care, I don't care.
さ、 気にしない、気にしない
I guess it's fine as long as I can drink it.
とりあえず飲めればいいや、みたいなね
Well, if you could give me some toast, please.
や っぱね、トーストってくれたらね、
Whether it's water or tea,
お水だったりさ、お茶だったりさ、
It ends up looking like that,
そういう感じになっちゃうんだけど、
After all, it doesn't matter.
やっぱ、関係ない
It's definitely milk tea.
全然、ミルクティーだったりね
I thought it wouldn't fit.
合わないだろっていうのが
I see.
なるほどね
What do you and your boyfriend do? Where do you usually eat?
彼氏とはさ、なに、普段さ、どういうところでご飯とか食べるの?
Family restaurant?
ファミレス?
Well, that's right, it's affordable.
まあそうだよね、ディーズナブルだもんね
I see.
そっか
What do you like?
なに好きなの?
なに好き?
What, uh, what is it, Yuki-chan?
なんかさ、あのー、なんだっけ、ゆきちゃんはさ、
When I said what I like, I said what I don't like.
なに好きって言ったときにさ、 苦手なもの言ってた
Yes, I received a lot of things that I wasn't good at.
そう、苦手なもの、いっぱいもらったじゃん
Yeah, I said it.
うん、言った
Anything other than pumpkin, shiitake mushrooms, green peppers, and carrots,
かぼちゃ、椎茸、ピーマン、ニンジン以外なら、
I like everything.
なんでも好きです
He says he likes everything.
なんでも好きですってね
By the way, pumpkin, carrot, shiitake mushroom,
ちなみにかぼちゃ、ニンジン、椎茸、
Not really.
ないっすね
ないですね
Not really.
ないっすね
copper?
どう?
Can you eat it?
食える?
not at all.
全然
What about vegetables?
野菜は?
Can I eat lettuce?
レタスとか食べれる?
Oh, I eat a lot.
ああ、よく食べます
Really?
本当に?
Then, yeah, you can eat it at all.
したらじゃあ、うん、全然食べちゃっていいよ
I agree.
そうですね
Yeah.
うん
There are a lot of salads.
なんかサラダ多いね
I agree.
そうだね
This, this, what is this?
これ、これな、これなにこれ?
this.
これ
This is a salad for lunch.
これ、ランチのサラダです
Ah, salad for lunch.
あ、ランチのサラダね
It looks like a salad for lunch.
ランチのサラダらしいですわ
It's like a lot, a lot, a lot,
なんか いっぱい、いっぱい、いっぱいなんか、
The vegetables have arrived.
お野菜来ちゃったけど
Should I eat Toyota?
トヨタ食べたらいいかな
Yeah, um, it's totally fine.
うん、あの、全然いいよ
Yeah.
うん
So, how about I give you some recommendations?
じゃあ、おすすめ分けしたらいい?
Shall I recommend it?
おすすめ分けしようか
Well then, I'll give you some recommendations.
じゃあ、おすすめ分けしてあげるね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This is a good lunch salad.
これ、ランチサラダはいいね
This is a salad for lunch.
これ、ランチのサラダば
Yeah, this is good.
うん、これいいや
Don't eat this.
こっち食べな
Over here.
こっちね
Can you eat it?
食べれる?
Yeah.
うん
cute.
かわいい
I'll eat it properly.
いただきますちゃんとすんだ
Yes, I will.
え、しますよ
Looks good.
いいそう
picture?
え?
There are some girls who don't like itadakimasu.
いただきますしない女の子もいるんだよ
Yes, I'll just eat it.
します よ、いただきますぐらい
delicious?
おいしい?
Do you like fruit?
フルーツ好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
I like Maseno.
マセノ好きなんだ
マセノ好きです
like?
好き?
But it's gotten a little bigger.
でもちょっと大きくなりました
lie?
うそ?
Yeah.
うん
Really?
本当に?
ERROR
この1ヶ月間で?
My boyfriend told me.
彼氏に言われました
Seriously?
マジ?
It got a little bigger.
少し大きくなった
What, so your boyfriend already rubs you every day?
何、じゃあもう彼氏に毎日揉まれてんの?
So, what, it looks like your hormones made you grow a bit?
で、何、ホルモンでちょっと大きくなっちゃったみたいな?
perhaps.
たぶん
Oh, that's it, uh, okay?
え、それさ、あの、大丈夫?
Isn't there something in it?
なんか、入れてない?
Didn't it get bigger after you put it in?
入れて大きくなったとかじゃない?
this?
これ?
yes.
そう
I don't want an injection even though it hurts.
いやだ、痛いのに注射絶対
Let's stop doing that.
そういうのはやめようね
Oh, no, you don't have to eat it.
あ、いや食べなくていいよ
You don't hate eating like that, right?
そんな食べ、嫌いないでしょ?
Carrot.
ニンジン
I'll eat it, absolutely.
食べますよ、全然
It's a carrot, right?
ニンジンでしょ?
It's a carrot.
ニンジンです
Didn't you say you hate carrots?
ニンジン嫌いって言わなかった?
I hate it but I eat it.
嫌いだけど食べる
Uncle, I hate carrots, so...
おじさんニンジン嫌いだから、もう、
That person eating carrots, uh...
あのニンジン食ってる人を、あの、
Rejection reaction.
拒絶反応
Do you want to eat?
食べます?
No, but you don't have to force yourself to eat it.
いや、だけど無理して食べなくていいよ
Oh, but hey, you can eat it.
え、でもねえねえ食べれますよ
Wow, that's great.
すごい、偉いね
yeah?
ん?
Things that aren't delicious, by nature.
美味しくないもの、本来
What, what do you mean the cup size has gotten bigger?
え、何、カップ数が大きくなったってこと?
Will the number of cups remain the same?
カップ数は変わんない?
It's not subtle.
微妙ならない
Eh, no, the size of the graphics is also a bit...
え、じゃない、グラのサイズも、ちょっと、
What is it? Has it gotten a little bigger?
なんだっけ、なんかちょっと大きくなった?
Well, depending on the thing, I guess I'll change it a little bit.
いや、物によって、まぁちょっと大きく変えようかな、
Like.
みたいな
Oh really?
あ、ほんとに?
No, it's just a little bit.
いや、物少しですよ
Hey, nice, nice.
へえ、いいねいいね
Don't eat too much.
いっぱいじゃあ食べなよ
Eat more.
もっといっぱい食べなよ
Don't make it much bigger.
もっといっぱい大きくしない
After D, there's E, and then there's E.
Dの次はEだね、そしたらね
Yeah, yeah.
うん、うん
What do you ideally want to be?
理想はどんぐらいになりたいの?
No, I like it the way it is now.
いや、今のまんまがいいです
Oh, isn't it a big hole?
あ、大きく穴としてないの?
It's good to eat.
食べるのがいいです
I like how it's stretched out.
張ってるまんまがいい
I see.
なるほどね
Nobu-san, do you like it when we go out?
のぶさん、出かければ好き?
Nobu-san, I like it when you go out naturally.
のぶさん、天然で出かければ好き
I see.
なるほど
Well, I like things that men don't have.
さ あ、男性にないものはやっぱ好きよね
Hmm.
うーん
It doesn't matter.
どうでもいいね
Yeah.
うん
Add shrimp to chili sauce.
エビのチリソースに入れてください
Can I have curry too?
カレーも食べれる?
Yeah.
うん
Can you eat it?
食べれる?
Can you eat shrimp?
エビ食べれる?
Yeah.
うん
I cut a lot.
いっぱい切ったよ
That orange definitely won't match.
絶対合わないよ、そのオレンジずつ
I don't think it fits.
合わないと思ってます
Really?
本当に?
But it's good if you can drink it.
だけど飲めればいいもんね
As long as I can drink it.
飲めればいい
It's the same if you put it in a shrimp bag.
エビ袋に入れば一緒
Yeah.
うん
Well then, let's go eat.
じゃあ、食べていこうか
Can I cut it once?
一回切っていい?
Yuki-chan, are you full?
ゆきちゃん、お腹いっぱいになった?
Yeah, a lot.
うん、いっぱい
Good, good.
よかったよかった
Was it delicious?
おいしかった?
Yeah.
うん
It was delicious.
おいしかったね
おいしかったです
Well, that means I'm full,
したらじゃあ、お腹いっぱいになったということだから、
Can I eat it this time?
今度こそ食べていい?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
This time.
今度こそ
Shall we go to the hotel and eat sometime?
今度こそホテル行って、食べようか
how was it?
どうだった?
It was delicious.
おいしかったね
good.
よかった
I'm glad you came, then.
来てよかったね、じゃあ
Okay, let's go to the hotel, well, just like at the beginning,
じゃあ、ホテル行って、まあね、冒頭でもちょっと行ってさ、
I want to tinker with it.
いじくり回したいな
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
I don't know though.
分かんないけど
Well, you know, over here, over here.
まあ、あの、こっちに、こっちっていうかさ、
Well, what do you say to your uncle?
まあ、おじさんにさ、あの、なんていうの、
I feel like it would be okay if I could leave my body with you.
体預けてくれれば、いいかなって感じ
Well, is it okay to leave it as it is?
まあ、そのまんまの状態でいい?
Then, this time, then,
そしたらじゃあ、今度こそ、じゃあ、
I'm going to the hotel.
ホテル行くから
I'm full.
お腹いっぱいになった
hey.
ね
You finally arrived at the hotel.
やっとホテル着いたね
I have arrived.
着きました
hey.
ね
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
Yeah, a little bit.
うん、ちょっと
a little bit?
ちょっと?
Are you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張してる?
I'm a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張してる
That's right.
そうだよね
Well.
まあね
It's a better hotel than last time, isn't it?
前回よりさ、いいホテルでしょ?
surely.
確かに
Right?
でしょ?
It was a little cramped last time.
前回ちょー狭かったじゃん
It was very small.
全然狭かった
Well, I'm sorry, I'm really sorry at that time.
で、ごめん、あの時はさ、まじごめん
I wasn't really into it at that time.
本当に入ってなかった、あの時は
So I worked hard to find a hotel.
だからホテル探しちょっと頑張ったじゃん
I did my best.
頑張った
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
I remember.
覚えてる
yes.
そう
At that time, I worked really hard to find a hotel.
あの時めちゃくちゃホテル探し頑張ってさ、
What can I say now?
もう、なんていうの
I'm saying, "There's no hotel, there's no hotel."
ホテルねーねーねーねー言いながらさ、
I had no choice but to go into that hotel.
仕方なくあのホテル入ってさ、 ちょっとあのー、
What do you mean?
なんていうの
I think it was a little difficult,
ちょっと大変だった思いっていうのがさ、
That was it though.
あれだったけど
This time, it's a little wider, to a certain extent.
今回はさ、ある程度さ、ちょっと広いし、
Well, there are things like that,
ちょっと、そういうのもあるから、
That's kind of what I said earlier,
ちょっとそういうので、さっき言ったさ、
I thought I'd like to mess with it.
いじり倒したいなーと思ってね
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そうそうそうそう
What do you say?
なんて言うの
Just to the extent possible,
可能な範囲までさ、ちょっと、
You look like you're going to cry.
泣 きそうだね
You don't look like you're going to cry.
泣 きそうじゃないよねー
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Don't you feel like crying?
泣きそうじゃない?
I don't feel like crying.
泣きそうじゃない
So it's within the realm of possibility.
だからちょっと可能な範囲内でさ、
I thought I'd give it a try,
ちょっとやってみようよっていうのでさ、
Yuki-chan is cute, so you can leave her as she is.
ゆきちゃん可愛いからさ、そのままの状態でいいから、
The rest is over here, to the old men.
あとはもうこっちに、おじさんたちにね、
If you entrust your body to me, Yuki-chan too,
体を預けてくれれば、 あとゆきちゃんもね、
I hope you can do it.
やってくれればいいから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It makes me a little nervous.
ちょっと緊張するよね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
I might be nervous, but...
緊張もさ、するかもしんないけど、
Hey, that's it, just do it while maintaining a good sense of tension.
ちょっと ね、それはそれでね、 いい緊張感を保ちながらやって
Let's go.
い こうよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's okay.
大丈夫ねー
Well, let's do it downstairs.
じゃあ下でやっていくね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Suddenly, the number of words increased again.
急にまた、口数が
I started to get nervous.
緊張し始めた
I'm nervous.
緊張して
So, how does it compare to a paddle?
で、かいと比べたらどう?
Because I'm less nervous.
緊張は少ないから
few?
少 ない?
You defeated me for a while, right?
一時倒してくれたよね?
Yeah.
うん
Is that okay?
そういうことでいい?
That's fine.
それ、そういうことでいい
real?
ほんと?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Did you defeat it once?
一時倒した?
Will you be defeated?
倒される?
Yeah.
うん
You seem to be fine.
元気みたいだな
Even for a year, you were in good spirits.
1年間でもね、 元気あったんだよね
Yeah.
うん
It's too realistic to call it cosplay though.
コスプレと言えないぐらいのリアスさだけど
not at all.
全然
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
But, here and there,
だけど、 なんかちょいちょい、 そこかしこに、
There's some kind of markings,
なんかこう、マーキングみたいなのがあるんだけど、
Bun-chan, can I mark it?
ぶんちゃん、マーキングしてていい?
Hey, are you in trouble?
ほら、困る?
I'm in trouble.
困っちゃう
Look, I'm in trouble.
ほ ら、困っちゃう
This is cooing.
クースしてんだね、これね
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
I'll probably go in either way.
入っちゃうね、どっちかもね
can?
できる?
You can do it.
でき るね
It went in well.
しっかり入ったよ
I could see the ivy from earlier.
さっきのツタシが見えた